<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-05-17T18:54:12-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Dark Web Security - Tor onion links</title><subtitle>Dark Web Security - Tor onion links.</subtitle><author><name>Paul Syverson</name></author><entry><title type="html">How To Safely Access Dark Web</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/how-to-safely-access-dark-web/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How To Safely Access Dark Web" /><published>2023-05-17T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-05-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/how-to-safely-access-dark-web</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/how-to-safely-access-dark-web/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;how-to-safely-access-the-dark--deep-web&quot;&gt;How to safely access the Dark &amp;amp; Deep web&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Even if you use the internet on a daily basis – writing emails and styling with your YouTube skills – there may still be uncharted lands on your Internet map. What if I told you that you can only see a fraction of the things the Internet has to offer?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beneath the surface, there is a much deeper layer that is inaccessible via your common browser – the dark web and deep web. But accessing this part of the net is not very safe unless you take certain precautions. So make yourself comfortable in your seat and learn how you can safely access the Dark and Deep web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;guide-on-how-to-access-the-deep-and-the-dark-web-safely&quot;&gt;Guide on how to access the Deep and the Dark web safely&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your connection with Tor passes through three publicly hosted nodes chosen randomly before reaching the intended website. However, many users prefer to opt for additional measures to go the extra mile when it comes to privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many options to pick from: for an additional privacy-minded OS like Tails, Qubes OS or Whonix, burner laptops, etc. Finally download Tor browser from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Tor Project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;know-your-goal&quot;&gt;Know your goal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t take much IT knowledge to realize that the Deep web (and especially the Dark web) is a pretty dangerous place. Especially if you don’t know what you’re doing and only go there to satisfy your morbid curiosity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, you have to know what exactly you are going to do there so that you don’t end up being a victim of a hacker with all of your personal info exposed (which is much more likely than on the surface web).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;take-safety-precautions&quot;&gt;Take safety precautions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have to take into consideration all the applications that are currently running on your computer.
For example, you should close all the apps that you have accounts for. This includes your password manager, streaming applications like Netflix, and storage apps like OneDrive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might even think about closing everything that’s not essential for browsing the Deep web. Also, you should cover your webcam (if you’re not doing this already) and turn off the location on your device. In addition to all this, you must have a quality antivirus software tool installed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;check-for-ip-leaks&quot;&gt;Check for IP leaks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though you have everything set up, there’s still something to be done, and it’s checking whether you have any leaks that could reveal any personal info about you. Basically, you have to check for IP, DNS, and WebRTC leaks. For this, you should head to ipleak.net and dnsleaktest.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There, you should check whether the IP address displayed is your real one or the one provided by Tor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;find-a-website-and-connect&quot;&gt;Find a website and connect&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can check our onion links section in the navigation bar or visit this &lt;a href=&quot;/links/&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Paul Syverson</name></author><summary type="html">How to safely access the Dark &amp;amp; Deep web Even if you use the internet on a daily basis – writing emails and styling with your YouTube skills – there may still be uncharted lands on your Internet map. What if I told you that you can only see a fraction of the things the Internet has to offer?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What Is Dark Web</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/what-is-dark-web/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What Is Dark Web" /><published>2023-05-17T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-05-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/what-is-dark-web</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/what-is-dark-web/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;what-is-the-dark-web-how-to-access-it-and-what-youll-find&quot;&gt;What is the dark web? How to access it and what you’ll find&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The dark web is part of the internet that isn’t visible to search engines and requires the use of an anonymizing browser called Tor to be accessed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dark-web-definition&quot;&gt;Dark web definition&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dark web is a part of the internet that isn’t indexed by search engines. You’ve no doubt heard talk of the “dark web” as a hotbed of criminal activity — and it is. Researchers Daniel Moore and Thomas Rid of King’s College in London classified the contents of 2,723 live dark web sites over a five-week period in 2015 and found that 57% host illicit material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A 2019 study, Into the Web of Profit, conducted by Dr. Michael McGuires at the University of Surrey, shows that things have become worse. The number of dark web listings that could harm an enterprise has risen by 20% since 2016. Of all listings (excluding those selling drugs), 60% could potentially harm enterprises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can buy credit card numbers, all manner of drugs, guns, counterfeit money, stolen subscription credentials, hacked Netflix accounts and software that helps you break into other people’s computers. Buy login credentials to a $50,000 Bank of America account, counterfeit $20 bills, prepaid debit cards, or a “lifetime” Netflix premium account. You can hire hackers to attack computers for you. You can buy usernames and passwords.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not everything is illegal, the dark web also has a legitimate side. For example, you can join a chess club or BlackBook, a social network described as the “the Facebook of Tor.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: This post contains links to dark web sites that can only be accessed with the Tor browser, which can be downloaded for free at https://www.torproject.org.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;deep-web-vs-dark-web-whats-the-difference&quot;&gt;Deep web vs. dark web: What’s the difference?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The terms “deep web” and “dark web” are sometimes used interchangeably, but they are not the same. Deep web refers to anything on the internet that is not indexed by and, therefore, accessible via a search engine like Google. Deep web content includes anything behind a paywall or requires sign-in credentials. It also includes any content that its owners have blocked web crawlers from indexing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Medical records, fee-based content, membership websites, and confidential corporate web pages are just a few examples of what makes up the deep web. Estimates place the size of the deep web at between 96% and 99% of the internet. Only a tiny portion of the internet is accessible through a standard web browser—generally known as the “clear web”.
Nominations are open for the 2024 Best Places to Work in IT&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dark web is a subset of the deep web that is intentionally hidden, requiring a specific browser—Tor—to access, as explained below. No one really knows the size of the dark web, but most estimates put it at around 5% of the total internet. Again, not all the dark web is used for illicit purposes despite its ominous-sounding name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dark-web-tools-and-services&quot;&gt;Dark web tools and services&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Into the Web of Profit report identified 12 categories of tools or services that could present a risk in the form of a network breach or data compromise:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Infection or attacks, including malware, distributed denial of service (DDoS) and botnets
Access, including remote access Trojans (RATs), keyloggers and exploits
Espionage, including services, customization and targeting
Support services such as tutorials
Credentials
Phishing
Refunds
Customer data
Operational data
Financial data
Intellectual property/trade secrets
Other emerging threats
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The report also outlined three risk variables for each category:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Devaluing the enterprise, which could include undermining brand trust, reputational damage or losing ground to a competitor
Disrupting the enterprise, which could include DDoS attacks or other malware that affects business operations
Defrauding the enterprise, which could include IP theft or espionage that impairs a company&apos;s ability to compete or causes a direct financial loss
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) kits have been available on the dark web for several years, but those offerings have become far more dangerous with the rise of specialized criminal groups like REvil or GandCrab. These groups develop their own sophisticated malware, sometimes combined with pre-existing tools, and distribute them through “affiliates”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The affiliates distribute the ransomware packages through the dark web. These attacks often include stealing victims’ data and threatening to release it on the dark web if the ransom isn’t paid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This business model is successful and lucrative. IBM Security X-Force, for example, reported that 29% of its ransomware engagements in 2020 involved REvil. The criminal groups that developed the malware gets a cut of the affiliates’ earnings, typically between 20% and 30%. IBM estimates that REvil’s profits in the past year were $81 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dark-web-browser&quot;&gt;Dark web browser&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All this activity, this vision of a bustling marketplace, might make you think that navigating the dark web is easy. It isn’t. The place is as messy and chaotic as you would expect when everyone is anonymous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accessing the dark web requires the use of an anonymizing browser called Tor. The Tor browser routes your web page requests through a series of proxy servers operated by thousands of volunteers around the globe, rendering your IP address unidentifiable and untraceable. Tor works like magic, but the result is an experience that’s like the dark web itself: unpredictable, unreliable and maddeningly slow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, for those willing to put up with the inconvenience, the dark web provides a memorable glimpse at the seamy underbelly of the human experience – without the risk of skulking around in a dark alley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dark-web-search-engine&quot;&gt;Dark web search engine&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dark web websites look pretty much like any other site, but there are important differences. One is the naming structure. Instead of ending in .com or .co, dark web websites end in .onion. That’s “a special-use top level domain suffix designating an anonymous hidden service reachable via the Tor network,” according to Wikipedia. Browsers with the appropriate proxy can reach these sites, but others can’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dark web websites also use a scrambled naming structure that creates URLs that are often impossible to remember. For example, a popular search index site called The Hidden Wiki goes by the unintelligible address of “wiki5pbx73nfvmd7lug3siudagdbbdli7ta4ed2cklux4bbd6utc5byd.onion”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Law enforcement officials are getting better at finding and prosecuting owners of sites that sell illicit goods and services. In the summer of 2017, a team of cyber cops from three countries successfully shut down AlphaBay, the dark web’s largest source of contraband, sending shudders throughout the network. But many merchants simply migrated elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The anonymous nature of the Tor network also makes it especially vulnerable to DDoS, said Patrick Tiquet, Director of Security &amp;amp; Architecture at Keeper Security, and the company’s resident expert on the topic. “Sites are constantly changing addresses to avoid DDoS, which makes for a very dynamic environment,” he said. As a result, “The quality of search varies widely, and a lot of material is outdated.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;for-sale-on-the-dark-web&quot;&gt;For sale on the dark web&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dark web has flourished thanks to bitcoin, the crypto-currency that enables two parties to conduct a trusted transaction without knowing each other’s identity. “Bitcoin has been a major factor in the growth of the dark web, and the dark web has been a big factor in the growth of bitcoin,” says Tiquet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nearly all dark web commerce sites conduct transactions in bitcoin or monero, but that doesn’t mean it’s safe to do business there, but what do you expect when buying guns or drugs is your objective?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dark web commerce sites have the same features as any e-retail operation, including ratings/reviews, shopping carts and forums, but there are important differences. One is quality control. When both buyers and sellers are anonymous, the credibility of any ratings system is dubious. Ratings are easily manipulated, and even sellers with long track records have been known to suddenly disappear with their customers’ crypto-coins, only to set up shop later under a different alias.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most e-commerce providers offer some kind of escrow service that keeps customer funds on hold until the product has been delivered. However, in the event of a dispute don’t expect service with a smile. It’s pretty much up to the buyer and the seller to duke it out. Every communication is encrypted, so even the simplest transaction requires a PGP key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even completing a transaction is no guarantee that the goods will arrive. Many need to cross international borders, and customs officials are cracking down on suspicious packages. The dark web news site Deep.Dot.Web teems with stories of buyers who have been arrested or jailed for attempted purchases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-the-dark-web-illegal&quot;&gt;Is the dark web illegal?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We don’t want to leave you with the impression that everything on the dark web is nefarious or illegal. The Tor network began as an anonymous communications channel, and it still serves a valuable purpose in helping people communicate in environments that are hostile to free speech. “A lot of people use it in countries where there’s eavesdropping or where internet access is criminalized,” Tiquet said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to learn all about privacy protection or cryptocurrency, the dark web has plenty to offer. There are a variety of private and encrypted email services, instructions for installing an anonymous operating system and advanced tips for the privacy-conscious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s also material that you wouldn’t be surprised to find on the public web, such as links to full-text editions of hard-to-find books, collections of political news from mainstream websites and a guide to the steam tunnels under the Virginia Tech campus. You can conduct discussions about current events anonymously on Intel Exchange. There are several whistleblower sites, including a dark web version of Wikileaks. Pirate Bay, a BitTorrent site that law enforcement officials have repeatedly shut down, is alive and well there. Even Facebook has a dark web presence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“More and more legitimate web companies are starting to have presences there,” Tiquet said. “It shows that they’re aware, they’re cutting edge and in the know.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s also plenty of practical value for some organizations. Law enforcement agencies keep an ear to the ground on the dark web looking for stolen data from recent security breaches that might lead to a trail to the perpetrators. Many mainstream media organizations monitor whistleblower sites looking for news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;staying-on-top-of-the-hacker-underground&quot;&gt;Staying on top of the hacker underground&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keeper’s Patrick Tiquet checks in regularly because it’s important for him to be on top of what’s happening in the hacker underground. “I use the dark web for situational awareness, threat analysis and keeping an eye on what’s going on,” he said will. “I want to know what information is available and have an external lens into the digital assets that are being monetized – this gives us insight on what hackers are targeting.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are also many tools that can be use to monitor the dark web and scan for personally identifiable information and even respond to attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you find your own information on the dark web, there’s precious little you can do about it, but at least you’ll know you’ve been compromised. Bottom line: If you can tolerate the lousy performance, unpredictable availability, and occasional shock factor of the dark web, it’s worth a visit.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Paul Syverson</name></author><summary type="html">What is the dark web? How to access it and what you’ll find The dark web is part of the internet that isn’t visible to search engines and requires the use of an anonymizing browser called Tor to be accessed.</summary></entry></feed>